[
    {
         "cell_ids": [
             1
         ],
         "question": "How many different categories are there in the BBC News dataset?",
         "answer": "5",
         "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
         "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
     },
      {
         "cell_ids": [
              5
          ],
         "question": "How many articles are in the training dataset?",
         "answer":"1490",
         "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
         "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
     },
      {
         "cell_ids": [
             5
          ],
          "question": "What are the column names of the train dataset?",
         "answer": "ArticleId, Text, Category",
         "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
     },
     {
        "cell_ids": [
            12
         ],
          "question": "What is the name of the column that contains the text to be used for model training?",
          "answer": "'clean_text'",
          "task":"Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill":"Basic Data Analysis"
     },
     {
         "cell_ids": [
           12
         ],
         "question": "What is the name of the column that contains the labels for each article in the training data?",
          "answer": "'Category'",
           "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
     },
   {
         "cell_ids": [
              17
         ],
         "question": "What is the mean of the number of words in each article?",
         "answer": "401",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
     },
       {
         "cell_ids": [
              17,18
         ],
         "question": "What is the number of articles after removing outliers based on number of words",
         "answer": "1484",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
     },
     {
         "cell_ids": [
             23
         ],
        "question": "What is the accuracy of the matrix factorization model on training data?",
          "answer": "0.9609164420485176",
          "task": "Topic Modeling",
          "skill": "Latent Semantic Analysis"
     },
        {
         "cell_ids": [
           25
          ],
        "question": "What are the topics identified in the articles by matrix factorization?",
          "answer": "Business, tech, politics, sport, entertainment",
         "task": "Topic Modeling",
          "skill": "Latent Semantic Analysis"
     },
     {
         "cell_ids": [
             27
         ],
          "question": "Based on the clustering, what category does \"cutting tool\" belong to?",
         "answer": "Cluster 4",
         "task":"Topic Modeling",
         "skill": "Latent Semantic Analysis"
     }
 ]